capemaycountyherald.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy | Site | capemaycountyherald.com

Effective as of April 16, 2012

Seawave Corporation d/b/a Cape May County Herald (“Company”, “we” or “us”) provides this “Privacy Policy” to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information received from users on our website at www.capemaycountyherald.com or our Facebook Application (collectively, the “Site”). This Privacy Policy applies to information collected on the Site and is incorporated by reference into the Visitor Agreement.

 **Scope**

This Privacy Policy applies to user information collected as explained below from visitors, “Members” (as defined in the Visitor Agreement), advertisers, posters, and others who visit the Site.

 **Collected Information and Use**

We do not require registration for visitors to peruse the Site. Some services offered on our Site do require registration. The information we gather falls into two categories: (1) “Personal Information”, some of which is required, such as name, city, state, zip code, and email address, that you voluntarily supply (for example, when you register as a Member of the Site or customize our Site to provide you with information specific to your neighborhood), and (2) information gathered on usage patterns and preferences as you navigate through our Site (“Non-Personal Information”).

 **How we Collect Information**

Our web pages may contain electronic images (called “single-pixel GIFs” or “web beacons”) that allow us and our vendors to count users who have visited particular pages or to access certain cookies. We may use these tools and other technologies to recognize which pages users visit, and which links they click on. These features may also be included in our email newsletters so that we can learn which messages have been opened and acted upon. We may also be able to verify your online purchases from us or from third party sites that have agreed to share such information with us.

We may receive Personal Information about you from third parties, including, for example, information about your transactions, purchase history, or relationships with various product and service providers, and your use of certain applications. For example, if you access an Online Service through a third party connection or log-in, such as Facebook Connect, that third party may pass certain information about your use of its service to us. This information could include, but is not limited to, the user ID associated with your account, any information you have permitted the third party to share with us, and any information you have made public in connection with that service.

 **Browser Information and IP Addresses**

Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer configuration when you visit our site, including the type of browser software you use, the operating system you are running, the resolution of your computer monitor, the website that referred you, and your IP address. (Your IP address is a numerical address that is used by computers connected to the Internet to identify your computer so that data such as the web pages you want to view can be transmitted to you.) We also use IP address information for systems administration and trouble shooting purposes. Your IP address does not tell us who you are. We use this information to deliver web pages to you upon request, to tailor our site to the interests of our users, and to measure traffic within our site.

We use your Personal Information to register you as a Member, facilitate your use of the Site, respond to your inquiries, contact you for customer services purposes, enable you to enjoy and easily navigate the Site, better understand your needs and interests, inform you about the services offered on our Site or of important changes or additions to the Site, and to send you newsletters, offers, and information that you request or that we think may interest you. To deliver relevant content and recommendations. To make your experience more interesting and personalized, we may use any of the Personal and Other Information we collect to assist us in delivering content on our Online Services.

We also collect the Non-Personal Information that you provide as part of registering on the Site which we may combine with aggregate information collected from other Site users to attempt to provide you with a better experience, improve the quality and value of the Site, and provide to vendors of products and services offered through our Site. We may also track and analyze Non-Personal Information identifying and aggregating usage and volume statistical information from our visitors, and monitor the behavior of our users, to generate and derive useful data and information concerning the interests, characteristics and website use behavior of our users, and to verify that visitors to the Site meet the criteria required to process their requests.

 **Contests and Promotions**

From time to time, we may offer contests, sweepstakes or other promotions (“Sweepstakes”) on the Site. If you enter one of these promotions, you will have to provide Personal Information, as requested, so that we can contact you if you win. We may share this information with any wholly or majority-owned subsidiary of the Company and any co-sponsor of the Sweepstakes (we will identify any co-sponsor in the official rules for the Sweepstakes). If you do not want us to collect the information requested in the Sweepstakes form or to provide it to any wholly or majority-owned subsidiary of the Company or contest co-sponsors, then please do not enter the contest or sweepstakes.

 **Email Newsletters**

We may offer you the opportunity to subscribe to email newsletters on topics that we believe are of interest to our visitors. If you have opted to receive a particular newsletter, you may always unsubscribe later if you decide not to receive further mailings of the newsletter from us. Please see the “Opt Out” section below.

 **Prohibited Uses**

This Site is not intended for use by persons located within the European Economic Area (EEA). We do not request or accept personal information concerning or supplied by persons who are located within the EEA at the time they access this Site. If you have accessed this Site from within the EEA, you should immediately discontinue your use. If you have supplied personal information to us in violation of this provision, whether through the registration of new user accounts or otherwise, please contact us at admin@cmcherald.com.

 **Information Sharing and Disclosure**

 **Members**

We will display your Personal Information in your profile page and elsewhere on the Site according to the preferences you set in your account. Any information you choose to provide should reflect how much you want all other Members to know about you. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information and we encourage Members to think carefully about what information about themselves they disclose in their profile pages. You can review and revise your profile information at any time.

 **Third Parties**

Except as specifically stated at the time we request information, or as provided for in this Privacy Policy, we do not disclose Personal Information to third parties. We may share Non-Personal Information with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and the creation of related reports. This information will not contain your Personal Information. We may take the information you provide and aggregate it with data from all the other people that use this Site and associated services. Then we would use that pool of information to inform third parties about our audience without identifying you personally. For example, we’ll be able to say to a third party: “We have 1,400 site visitors in this ZIP code,” which happens to be your location.

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Site’s services, to provide the services on the Site on our behalf or to perform Site-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management and improvement of the Site’s features). These third parties have access to your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to use it for any other purpose.

 **Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement.**

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of the Company or of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical, inappropriate or legally actionable.

 **Business Transfers**

We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

 **Links to Other Sites**

The Sites may contain links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other web sites. We encourage visitors and Members to check the privacy policy statements of these other web sites to understand their policies. Visitors and Members who access linked sites may be disclosing their private information. It is the responsibility of the visitor or Member to keep such information private and confidential.

 **Security**

Our Site has security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the data under our control. When our Site is accessed using Microsoft Internet Explorer versions 5.5 or higher and Mozilla Firefox, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology protects information using both server authentication and data encryption to help ensure that data is safe, secure, and available only to you. Members provide unique user names and passwords that must be entered each time a Member logs on to comment, review or update a profile. These safeguards help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of data. Members are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality and security of their user registrations and passwords.

 **Phishing**

We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your user identification, password, or social security or other national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail. In the event that you have technical difficulties and require support or troubleshooting and contact our technical support group, a technical representative may request your username and password. For more information about phishing, you may want to visit the Federal Trade Commission’s website at http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/pubs/consumer/alerts/alt127.htm

 **Cookies**

Like many websites, we use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize persistent cookies to save your username and password for future logins to the Site. Second, we utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Site, to better understand how you interact with the Site, and to monitor aggregate usage by users and web traffic routing on the Site. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you disconnect from the Site. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site. You can learn more about the use of cookies by visiting http://networkadvertising.org or http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie.

 **Changing or Deleting Your Information**

If you have registered on the Site as a Member and wish to update or change registration information, or wish to change your mind about receiving communications about our Site from us or any third party companies, then you may do so by visiting this link: www.capemaycountyherald.com and clicking on the “Log In” link. You may also contact us at admin@cmcherald.com specifying your new choice. Each email or newsletter that you receive from us will also include instructions on how to unsubscribe from future issues by using either a designated reply email address or hyperlink. Please note that if you completely delete such information, then your account may be deactivated.

 **Policy Toward Children**

The Site is not directed to children under 18 years old. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at admin@cmcherald.com. If we become aware that a child under 13 years old has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files. If you are under 13 years old and wish to access the Site, please consult your parents or guardian first.

 **Contact Us**

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of the Site should be directed to our Privacy Administrator, by e-mailing such questions to admin@cmcherald.com or by regular mail to: Seawave Corporation, 1508 Route 47, Rio Grande, NJ 08242.

©2018 Seawave Corporation. All rights reserved.
